A Guide to the Manuscripts of Joan Williams, 1966-1988
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Manuscripts of Joan Williams, 1966-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
9394-g,-h
This collection consists of 23 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The Library purchased this collection on March 4 and April 18, 1989.
Arrangement
These items are arranged alphabetically.
Contents List
- County Woman by Joan Williams, n.d., AMs (Box 1)
  This item consists of a partial draft of Chapter III.
- County Woman by Joan Williams, ca. 1982, TMs, 2 folders (Box 1)
  This item includes autograph changes and corrections, Chapter I-XXXI.
- County Woman by Joan Williams, ca. 1982, TMs, 3 folders (Box 1)
  This item includes autograph changes and corrections on yellow and white paper, Chapters I-XXXI.
- County Woman by Joan Williams, ca. 1982, TMs (EC), 2 folders (Box 2)
  This item consists of Chpaters I-XXXVII.
- County Woman by Joan Williams, ca. 1982, TMs (Box 2)
  This item consists of miscellaneous drafts of Chapters I-III, with autograph changes and coorections.
- County Woman by Joan Williams, ca. 1982, TMs (EC), 2 folders (Box 2)
  This item includes autograph changes and corrections, Chapters XV-XXXI.
- Old Powder Man by Joan Williams, 1966, AMs (Box 3)
  This item consists of a notebook kept by Joan Williams.
- Old Powder Man by Joan Williams, 1966, TMs, 3 folders (Box 3)
  This item consists of a setting copy, pages 1-457.
- Old Powder Man by Joan Williams, 1966, galley proofs (Box 3)
  This item consists of miscellaneous pages.
- Old Powder Man by Joan Williams, 1966, page proofs (Box 3)
  This item consists of a marked set.
- Pariah And Other Stories by Joan Williams, ca. 1983, TMs (Box 4)
  This item includes typescripts of three of the book's stories, "Jesse," "Going Ahead," and "Spring is Now."
- Pay the Piper by Joan Williams, ca. 1988, TMs, 3 folders (Box 4)
  This item includes autograph changes and corrections, Chapters I-XVI.
- Pay the Piper by Joan Williams, ca. 1988, TMs, 2 folders (Box 4)
  This item includes autograph changes and corrections, pages 101-425.
- Pay the Piper by Joan Williams, ca. 1988, TMs, 8 folders (Box 5)
  This item includes heavily revised drafts of the Prologue and Chapters I-V, with autograph changes.
- Pay the Piper by Joan Williams, ca. 1988, TMs, 5 folders (Box 6)
  This item includes heavily revised drafts of Chapters VI-XVIII, with autograph changes.
- Pay the Piper by Joan Williams, ca. 1988, TMs, 3 folders (Box 7)
  This item includes autograph changes and corrections of drafts of Chapters I-IX, XII, XII, and XIV.
- Pay the Piper by Joan Williams, ca. 1988, TMs (Box 7)
  This item consists of miscellaneous pages with autograph corrections and changes from early chapters, pages 31-56, 150, and 173.
- The Wintering by Joan Williams, ca. 1970, TMs (Box 7)
  This item includes revised miscellaneous pages with autograph corrections and changes.
- The Wintering by Joan Williams, ca. 1970, TMs, 6 folders (Box 8)
  This item consists of various typescripts corresponding to pages 1-369 in the published book, with autograph corrections and changes.
- The Wintering by Joan Williams, ca. 1970, TMs (Box 9)
  This item includes a typescript corresponding to pages 224-369 in the published book, with autograph corrections and changes.
- The Wintering by Joan Williams, 1970, TMs, 3 folders (Box 9)
  This item consists of a setting copy.
- The Wintering by Joan Williams, 1970, galleys, 2 folders (Box 9)
- The Wintering by Joan Williams, 1970, page proofs (Box 9)
  This item consists of an incomplete set.